<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mattmc3.github.io</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mattmc3.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 05:29:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Better shell aliases in git</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/07/better-shell-aliases-in-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 05:29:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/07/better-shell-aliases-in-git/</guid>
      <description>Better shell aliases in git: adding an external shell script 10 years ago, I read this blog post on GitHub Flow git aliases by Phil Haack. From it, I learned a few really clever tricks. Even though I never much cared for using &amp;lsquo;GitHub Flow&amp;rsquo; as a git workflow, I used some of those tricks for my own git aliases. One of those being this basic pattern:&#xA;[alias] foo = &amp;#34;!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two years of Colemak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018/02/two-years-of-colemak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 18:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018/02/two-years-of-colemak/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been more than 2 years since I learned to type using Colemak, and I am still happily using it. I have nearly no interaction with QWERTY aside from my phone, the occasional shared machine where I can&amp;rsquo;t use my AutoHotKey mappings, and the meaningless default letters on all the keyboards I use but never look at. I never quite achieved my goal of 85 WPM, but I also never really properly trained for speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colemak - the slowest way I could write a blog post (for now!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/01/colemak-the-slowest-way-i-could-write-a-blog-post-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 12:22:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/01/colemak-the-slowest-way-i-could-write-a-blog-post-for-now/</guid>
      <description>I am in the process of learning Colemak, an alternate keyboard layout. There are lots of great reasons to do something that seems so masochistic, but it would take too long to type them here (literally). I&amp;rsquo;ve gone from ~55 WPM, to about ~15-20, but my goal is ~80 COMFORTABLY by the time I&amp;rsquo;m done. The top of my right hand especially hurts after prolonged QWERTY use.&#xA;A couple guys at work use Dvorak, which I tried to learn in 2005.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
